#大家好 今天跟小豬 洗一下它的那個
Hi everyone! Today I'll wash the piggies, I mean, the,
#豬欄
pigsty.
#這個 快半個月沒跟它洗過啦
It ar, it hasn't been washed for almost half a month already.
#現在洗一下
I gonna wash it now.
#要搞鐵綫來
I need an iron wire.
#現在我給它沖一下
I'll flush it now.
#那個豬窩已經打掃乾淨啦 我去給點那個
The pigsty is already cleaned. I'll take the,
#給點這個稻草
give them some straw,
#跟這個南瓜 給它吃
and the pumpkins, to feed them.
#給點稻草給它們晚上做窩
Give them some straw to make the lair at night.
#給你稻草哦
Here's your straw!
#它們 它們晚上自己
They'll, They'll roll on the straw,
#自己會滾的 它們自己滾了個窩 (註︰有養過豬的嗎？我有沒有理解錯？)
roll on the straw at night to form the lair.
#給個南瓜給它 要把它摔爆哦
Give them a pumpkin. But I need to crash it first.
#要用力一點
Dump it hard!
#啊
Ah!
#吃啊
Now eat!
#好吃的
It's tasty.
#要把它摔爆
I'll crash it.
#用力過猛啦
I dumped to hard.
#豬吃的[SIC]多開心啊
See how happy they are?
#站起來捽
Crash on the bench.
#把它捽爆
Crash it!
#哇
Wa!
#沒摔爆
It's not crashed.
#小豬吃的[SIC]
The piggies are eating,
#多開心啊
so merrily.
#這稻草要給它們攤開一點
The straw, I need to spread it out for them.
#這南瓜
The pumpkin,
#堵在裡面了
get stuck here.
#好讓它們睡著這個窩
They now have a lair to sleep.
#你看 那條母豬懷孕了哦 又懷孕啦
Look! That female pig seems to be pregnant, pregnant again.
#等下一生的話又大把 (註︰這句不完全，有沒有更神似的翻譯？)
When it gives birth, a lot,
#現在都胖了好多
Now they're much fatter.
#前幾天瘦了
They were skinny a few days ago.
#小豬都好像
The piggies, it seems,
#找不到吃的 在這裡 關在這裡
that they don't have enough to eat, being here, shut off here.
#瘦了
So skinny.
#那麼壞的小豬豬 (註︰小豬豬......)
What a nasty little piggy!
#好啦 今天的視頻到這裡啦
Alright! The video ends here.
#天都快黑了 回家煮飯啦
It's getting dark now. I need to cook.